<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gildaswise</title>
    <link>https://gildaswise.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gildaswise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:19:25 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gildaswise.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sosin</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/sosin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 11:00:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/sosin/</guid>
      <description>Sosin is a messaging application focused on a fast and secure interaction between its users, currently available for on both Google Play Store and Apple&amp;rsquo;s App Store.
The main idea revolves around being able to only send and see one message at a time, which means there&amp;rsquo;s no history of your messages beside the most recent update. There are no advertisements inside the app, and the only way we earn something is through the process below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 13:13:16 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer who seeks to help people. Pretty normal, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? Maybe the musician part isn&amp;rsquo;t, which is a bonus.
I have a few albums published on Bandcamp and other streaming services, linked down below.
 Spotify Google Play iTunes Deezer Amazon Music  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working with Flutter since I graduated in march/2018, and I&amp;rsquo;ve published several apps with it: between a chat app with only one message, a manager for your car recalls (Brazil-only), a style-based social network and a pet breed detector, being the last two AI-driven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Match Maker&#39;s Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/match-maker-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 18:16:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/match-maker-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Gildásio Filho built the Match Maker app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Gildásio Filho at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/sosin-privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 12:59:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/sosin-privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>Gildásio Filho built the Sosin app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Gildásio Filho at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service and User Agreement</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/sosin-eula/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 12:59:55 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/sosin-eula/</guid>
      <description>By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should therefore make sure to read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter: Adding sign in with Google and phone authentication to your app</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/posts/flutter-phone-auth/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:19:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/posts/flutter-phone-auth/</guid>
      <description>This was my first tech related publication on any platform available and I&amp;rsquo;m kinda proud of the response! I just published it on dev.to and a few days ago on Medium.
It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting experience as while I was writing it, a lot of ideas about optimizing the code came and, well, I ended up doing them as you can see on the repo&amp;rsquo;s commit list.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
