<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Postagens on Gildaswise</title>
    <link>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Postagens on Gildaswise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:19:25 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Flutter: Adding sign in with Google and phone authentication to your app</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/flutter-autenticacao-telefone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 12:19:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/flutter-autenticacao-telefone/</guid>
      <description>This was my first tech related publication on any platform available and I&amp;rsquo;m kinda proud of the response! I just published it on dev.to and a few days ago on Medium.
It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting experience as while I was writing it, a lot of ideas about optimizing the code came and, well, I ended up doing them as you can see on the repo&amp;rsquo;s commit list.
I&amp;rsquo;m planning to do more tutorials like this for Flutter-related things as being part of the community like this is amazing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I kind of left this blog behind</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/deixado-de-lado/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 11:56:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/deixado-de-lado/</guid>
      <description>So, yeah. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;m not good enough doing these blog posts but I swear I&amp;rsquo;ll try to come here at least once a quarter write something about what I learned.
Almost a year has passed since my last post here and a lot happened since then.
First of all, I&amp;rsquo;m done with my graduation except some bureaucracy involving getting my degree itself. Second, I found someone amazing that I can&amp;rsquo;t even describe with words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little overview about side projects!</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/projetos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 11:56:25 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/projetos/</guid>
      <description>After a month I figured out that another post here would be something nice to do, right?
I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk a little about each of my current side projects as of this day, starting with my very first app: Studere, which is almost one year without updates. Yeah.
Studere is a fairly basic app, you can add scores by bimester (something apparently only used here in Brazil), create subjects, its appointments and tests and manage your schedule.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finalmente um blog!</title>
      <link>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/finalmente-um-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 22:54:36 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gildaswise.com/pt/postagens/finalmente-um-blog/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;ve finally decided to make a decent page here. I&amp;rsquo;m using Hugo as a &amp;ldquo;backend&amp;rdquo; and color me impressed with how easy it was to make everything work. Coder is the name of this beautiful and minimalistic theme and kudos to Luiz de Prá, the guy who made it!
I&amp;rsquo;ll try to make posts really as frequent as I can but this isn&amp;rsquo;t a promise.
Enjoy your stay and see you soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>